<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhonePinServiceRescuee</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="rescuesearch">Search For Survivors</string>
    <string name="toggleoff">Search for Help</string>
    <string name="toggleon">Please wait after turning this on. Try to conserve battery.</string>
    <string name="yes">About</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="large_text">\nAbout \n\nThis app is designed to assist in emergency response for disaster areas.  Many natural disasters and even man-made disasters create situations where citizens are badly harmed.  \nUnable to contact help due to local infrastructure also being destroyed, many people are left to hope for a passing Samaritans or rescuers who are blindly sifting through the rubble.  \nThe Disaster Rescue App is designed to be a beacon and emergency communication system that brings life-saving aid to you quicker by giving rescuers location, status updates, and search assistance. \n When unable to remove yourself from your situation the app will emit high pitch audio frequency SOS signals that will continue until you are rescued or the battery dies. This noise will alert human and canine rescuers to your presence.     \n</string>
    <string name="meshpng">meshpng</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="large_text1">The app can be turned on remotely by rescuers even when telecommunications have been disconnected through a mesh network of high range, low capacity communication extender nodes.   \nThis system is designed to work in conjunction with the disaster relief vehicles like the IEEEmoves van. This relief vehicle is specifically designed for restoring communications between disaster victims and loved-ones.   \nThe van uses a satellite dish to uplink with the internet even when power and telecommunication infrastructure has been destroyed. Before Diasater Rescue, this system could only provide internet access to the immediate area.   \nThis internet uplink can be stretched to a high range, low capacity telecommunication network with the addition of Sonnet communication extenders.  These devices are designed to create a temporary, low power communication network over a large area of wilderness. \n They do this by creating a mesh network of nodes relaying information and instructions from node to node until it arrives at the base station or end destination.   These nodes can be similarly deployed in disaster zones to create a communication network for rescuers to communicate and for emergency response services to be activated.   \n The Sonnet nodes can be deployed on rescuer’s vehicles, on their person, installed along the route, or flown out using drones. Any of these methods can quickly create a mobile mesh network that will continue to expand and interconnect as rescuers move farther from the base station.</string>
</resources>
